pioneer.co.in 2019-05-26

# Internet Leased Line Connection Hyderabad : Dedicated Leased Line : 1:1 Dedicated Internet Line

|   
---  
  
**     You are here >> Express Bandwidth **

Privacy & Policy: |   
---|---  
   
|    
---  
| General  
---  

The Company collects personal information when you register with the Company, when you use the Company products or services, when you visit the Company pages or the pages of certain partners of the Company. The Company may combine information about you that we have with information we obtain from business partners or other companies. The Company shall have the right to pass on the same to its business associates, franchisees without referring the same to you. 

• When you register we ask for information such as your name, email address, birth date, gender, zip code, occupation, industry, and personal     interests. Once you register with the Company and sign in to our services, you become our valued customer. 

• The Company collects information about your transactions with us and with some of our business partners, including information about your use of     products and services that we offer. 

• The Company can use information for the following general purposes: to customize the advertising and content you see, fulfill your requests for     products and services, improve our services, contact you, conduct research, and provide anonymous reporting for internal and external clients.   

Information Sharing and Disclosure   

| 

• The Company may share personal information about you with other people under the following circumstances:   
  
---  
  |  o We transfer information about you if the Company is acquired by or merged with another company under a different management. In this    event, the Company will notify you before information about you is transferred and becomes subject to a different privacy policy.   
  |  o We believe it is necessary to share information in order to investigate, prevent, or take action regarding illegal activities, suspected fraud,    situations involving potential threats to the physical safety of any person, violations of the Company's terms of use, or as otherwise required    by law.  
  | o We provide the information to trusted partners who work on behalf of or with the Company under confidentiality agreements. These companies    may use your personal information to help the Company communicate with you about offers from the Company and our marketing partners.  
• The Company plans to display targeted advertisements based on personal information. Advertisers (including ad serving companies) may assume    that people who interact with, view, or click on targeted ads meet the targeting criteria - for example, women ages 18-24 from a particular     geographic area.   
  | o The Company will not provide any personal information to the advertiser when you interact with or view a targeted ad. However, by interacting    with or viewing an ad you are consenting to the possibility that the advertiser will make the assumption that you meet the targeting criteria    used to display the ad.  
• The Company works with vendors, partners, advertisers, and service providers in many different industries and categories of business. 

• We reserve the right to send you certain communications relating to the Company's service, such as service announcements, administrative    messages and the Company's Newsletter, that are considered part of your account, without offering you the opportunity to opt-out of receiving    them.. Changes to this Privacy Policy The Company may update this policy and display the same in their website without notice to you and such    posting will be deemed to have been read by you.  

Changes to this Privacy Policy  
   
The Company may update this policy and display the same in their website without notice to you and such posting will be deemed to have been read by you.  

  Copyright Pioneer Elabs Limited 1998-2015  | Designed and Maintained by India Domain    
---|---
